<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bls12-381 on belijzajac.dev</title><link>https://belijzajac.dev/tags/bls12-381/</link><description>Recent content in bls12-381 on belijzajac.dev</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 17:44:15 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://belijzajac.dev/tags/bls12-381/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Proto-Danksharding: Speeding Up Blobs Verification</title><link>https://belijzajac.dev/proto-danksharding-speeding-up-blobs-verification/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 17:44:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://belijzajac.dev/proto-danksharding-speeding-up-blobs-verification/</guid><description>Introduction The Ethereum Foundation proposed EIP-4844 on February 25, 2022, with the objective of reducing gas fees. It introduces a new transaction type called &amp;ldquo;blob&amp;rdquo;, which is temporarily stored and committed using the KZG commitment scheme. In addition, the Ethereum Foundation developed a project called c-kzg-4844, which provides a minimal implementation of the polynomial commitments API written in C. This project does not use parallelization and exposes its C API for bindings in different programming languages.</description></item><item><title>Outperforming Rayon with OpenMP</title><link>https://belijzajac.dev/outperforming-rayon-with-openmp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 12:43:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://belijzajac.dev/outperforming-rayon-with-openmp/</guid><description>What’s it all about? For the Blockchain Technologies course, students were paired into groups and assigned to produce the fastest Rust library (crate) implementing the KZG10 scheme. Two teams used the same backend, that is, blst (implemented in assembly with direct bindings for Rust and C). The first team, blst-from-scratch, was using the said Rust bindings to produce an interface closer to c-kzg, whereas the ckzg team, which I was part of, was responsible for porting the latter over to Rust.</description></item></channel></rss>